<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>talon250 on Software Engineer</title><link>https://jamiebrunton.com/tags/talon250/</link><description>Recent content in talon250 on Software Engineer</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 10:07:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jamiebrunton.com/tags/talon250/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Talon 250 Pt1</title><link>https://jamiebrunton.com/posts/talon-250-pt1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 10:07:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jamiebrunton.com/posts/talon-250-pt1/</guid><description>The Maiden The talon has so far been an absolute breeze to build and fly. Putting the model together was as simple as gluing the tail on and placing the ZOHD Kohpilot inside.
One of the things mentioned quite frequently on this model is the durability of the wing support bracket, it is a balsa wood strip with a grab nut on the underside. Suffice to say, I&amp;rsquo;ll be adding to the list of people who think this part is weak, but probably not in the same scenario!</description></item><item><title>Talon 250 Build</title><link>https://jamiebrunton.com/posts/talon-250-build/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 12:09:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jamiebrunton.com/posts/talon-250-build/</guid><description>Intro Having already flown the bigger brother, the Mini Talon, I decided it would be nice to have a smaller, less intimidating plane to be able to launch in small spaces (parks and small fields). There&amp;rsquo;s so much to choose from these days in the low weight area, so much that you end up spoiled for choice!
In the end I chose to get the Talon 250 even after having a really poor experience with the original Nano Talon - the Nano Talon has been the only model I&amp;rsquo;ve been unable to successfully fly before destroying it&amp;hellip; R.</description></item></channel></rss>